const quiz = [
  //1
  {
    question: "In HTML, colors can be specified using HSL value, which means",
    options: [
      "High, Static, Low",
      "High, Stable, Low",
      "HTML, Semantics, Language",
      "Hue, Saturation, Light"],
    answer: "Hue, Saturation, Light"
  }, 
  //2
  {
    question: "A tag used as an alternative to make text bold is",
    options: [
      "&ltbold&gt",
      "&ltdouble&gt",
      "&ltstrong&gt",
      "&ltdark&gt"],
    answer: "&ltstrong&gt"
  },
  //3
  {
    question: "Attributes provided by &ltimg&gt tag of HTML are source file, width/height and",
    options: [
      "&ltalt&gt",
      "&ltlink&gt",
      "&ltdesign&gt",
      "&lthref&gt"],
    answer: "&ltalt&gt"
  },
  //4
  {
    question: "Elements &ltdiv&gt and &ltspan&gt are known to be",
    options: [
      "HTML formatting tags",
      "HTML grouping tags",
      "HTML container tags",
      "HTML listing tags"],
    answer: "HTML container tags"
  },
  //5
  {
    question: "In HTML, a hyperlink can be added as",
    options: [
      "&lta href='http://www.example.com'&gtExample&lt/a&gt",
      "&lta src='http://www.example.com'&gtexample&lt/a&gt",
      "&lta url='http://www.example.com'&gtexample&lt/a&gt",
      "&lta link='http://www.example.com'&gtexample&lt/a&gt"],
    answer: "&lta href='http://www.example.com'&gtExample&lt/a&gt"
  },
  //6
  {
    question: "For highlight text, HTML uses element said to be",
    options: [
      "&ltem&gt",
      "&ltimp&gt",
      "&ltmark&gt",
      "&lthighlight&gt"],
    answer: "&ltem&gt"
  },
  //7
  {
    question: "CSS stands for",
    options: [
      "Case Sensitive Sheets",
      "Cascading Style Sheets",
      "Cascading Sensitive Sheets",
      "Case Style Sheets"],
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheets"
  },
  //8
  {
    question: "A caption for &ltfieldset&gt element can be defined through element",
    options: [
      "&ltcap&gt",
      "&lttitle&gt",
      "&ltattfield&gt",
      "&ltlegend&gt"],
    answer: "&ltlegend&gt"
  },
  //9
  {
    question: "Method used by JavaScript to select a HTML element is",
    options: [
      "document.setElementById(class)",
      "document.setElementById(id)",
      "document.getElementById(id)",
      "document.getElementByClass(id)"],
    answer: "document.getElementById(id)"
  },
  //10
  {
    question: "In HTML, language of document is declared in tag",
    options: [
      "&lt!DOCTYPE html&gt",
      "&lthtml&gt",
      "&ltbody&gt",
      "&ltref&gt"],
    answer: "&lthtml&gt"
  }];
